const Questions = [
	{'question': "Who teaches charms at hogwarts?", 'answer': 'Professor Flitwick', 'b': 'Professor McGonagall', 'c': 'Professor Snape', 'd': 'Professor Dippet'},
	{'question': "How many houses at hogwarts?", 'answer': '4', 'b': '6', 'c': '3', 'd': '7'},
	{'question': "What is snapes mother called?", 'answer': 'Eileen Prince', 'b': 'Ginny Snape', 'c': 'Hermione Granger', 'd': 'Lavinder Brown'},
	{'question': "What is Hedwig?", 'answer': 'Owl', 'b': 'Student', 'c': 'Toad', 'd': 'Rat'},
	
	{'question': "What is Colin Creevey's younger brother called?", 'answer': 'Dennis', 'b': 'Roger', 'c': 'Cedric', 'd': 'Cormack'},
	{'question': "Who's beater bat did Cormac McLaggen take in his only quidditch match?", 'answer': 'Jimmy Peaks', 'b': 'Jack Sloper', 'c': 'Andrew Kirke', 'd': 'Fred Weasely'},
	{'question': "What is Gilderoy Lockhart's favourite color?", 'answer': 'Lilac', 'b': 'Midnight blue', 'c': 'Magenta', 'd': 'Turquoise'},
	{'question': "What is the Weasely twins 'constipation sensation that's gripping the nation' called?", 'answer': 'You know poo', 'b': 'All sort beans', 'c': 'Skiving snack box', 'd': 'Canary creams'},
	{'question': "What is the name of Barty Crouch's house elf he dismisses?", 'answer': 'Winky', 'b': 'Dobby', 'c': 'Hokey', 'd': 'Blinky'},
	{'question': "Who teaches the 6th year students to apperate?", 'answer': 'Wilkie Twycross', 'b': 'Albus Dumbledore', 'c': 'Professor Flitwick', 'd': 'Dedalus Diggle'},
]

module.exports = {
	Questions: Questions
};